Welcome back.
-: Bem vindo de volta.
I'm really excited to guide you through section 11.
Estou muito animado para gui-lo pela seo 11.
This is one of the most requested pieces of content
Este  um dos contedos mais solicitados
in any of my courses, and it involves scraping the web,
em qualquer um dos meus cursos, e envolve a explorao da web,
extracting information from websites
extraindo informaes de sites para que
so that you can use them in your Python programmes.
voc possa us-los em seus programas em Python.
For example, you may want to get all the news headlines
Por exemplo, voc pode querer obter todas as manchetes
from the BBC so that you don't have to go to the website
de notcias da BBC para que voc no
and try to look through the different pages,
tenha que ir ao site e tentar olhar atravs das diferentes
or you could download the scores of the NFL
pginas, ou voc pode baixar as pontuaes da NFL para
so that you don't have to go and look for them.
que voc don ' No tenho que ir procur-los.
There are many, many use cases for downloading websites
Existem muitos casos de uso para baixar sites
and extracting data from them.
e extrair dados deles.
And in this section, I'm really excited to present
E nesta seo, estou muito animado em
to you a unique way of structuring
apresentar a voc uma maneira nica de
your web scraping applications
estruturar seus aplicativos de raspagem de
that's gonna make it really easy for you to develop them.
pginas da web, o que tornar muito fcil desenvolv-los.
I'll see you in the next video.
Eu vou te ver no prximo vdeo.